# Alison A. Schreckengast Full-Stack Developer

alischreck@gmail.com, https://github.com/Alischrec, (985) 232-8839, Seattle, WA, https://alischrec.github.io/Portfolio/, https://www.linkedin.com/in/alison-schreckengast/

# SUMMARY:

Full stack web developer with an extensive background in psychology, literature, and client-side interactions. Currently working as a Technical Support Specialist utilizing my skills in solving client-facing issues as well as working closely with the development team.

## SKILLS:

Proficient: JavaScript ES6, HTML5, Node.js, Git, SQL, MySQL, GitHub, Object Oriented Programming, DDL &

DML, Material-UI, Bootstrap

Knowledgeable: Foundation, Azure DevOps

#### EMPLOYMENT:

Headset Inc., Technical Support Specialist - Seattle, WA, August 2018 - Present:

Actively provide technical support to various clients while troubleshooting basic technological issues. Work closely as a liaison between clients and the development team.

Headset Inc., Sales Development Representative - Seattle, WA, August 2017 - August 2018:

Made outbound calls to prospects and cultivated leads to develop relationships with prospective clients. Managed incoming live chats with prospective clients while also managing social media platforms and engaging with followers.

Darden Restaurants., Server/Bartender - Baton Rouge, LA, May 2013 - May 2018:

Provided a file dining experience to guests, including crafting specialty beverages while honing in on the skill of keeping a calm temperament under high-stress situations.

#### PROJECTS:

https://evening-springs-93825.herokuapp.com/ https://alischrec.github.io/Dumbbells and Donuts/

## **EDUCATION:**

University of Washington State Aug. 2020 - Feb. 2021 Full Stack Bootcamp Certificate

University of Louisiana Aug. 2012 - May 2017 B.S. in Science of Psychology & B.A. in English Literature, minor in Sociology